Guide to the New York Foundation For the Arts (NYFA) Records MSS.515
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII. Other NYFA Programs, 1970-2010; 45 linear feet in 45 record cartons
  - Subseries G. Cultural Blueprint, 1997-2002; 3 linear feet
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Drafts for Caron Atlas Article, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Table of Contents Drafts, Acknowledgments of Drafts, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Correspondence, Drafts for Articles, General Research, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Financing Examples and Other Research, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Correspondence and Research, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Correspondence After September 11th, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Correspondence and Research, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Funding Requests for Blueprint and Correspondence, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Contracts, Letters, and Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Budgetary Information For Blueprint, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Committee Members and Blueprint "Fact Sheet", 2001 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Correspondence, Photo Log, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Research, Meetings, Lists of Contacts, Meeting Minutes (hand-written), 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - "Culture Counts" Order Forms, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Mailing Agreement For Henry Street Settlement, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Requests for the Blueprint (E-mail and Letter), 2001 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Cultural Blueprint Press Releases, Pre and Post-September 11, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Post-September 11th Meetings, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Contacts Information, Committee Memberships, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Correspondence, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Meetings, Meeting Reports, Meeting Agendas, Correspondence, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Meeting Minutes in Progress, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Steering Committee Resumés, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Drafts of Steering Committee Plans, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Steering Committee Meetings, Agendas, Plans, Surveys, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Memos, Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Fordham University Study and Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Mapping Database and Printed Material, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Center for An Urban Future Materials, Press Articles, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Data on NYC, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Sources for Gathering Data, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Articles and Materials regarding Research for the Program, 1999-2001 (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Department of Cultural Affairs Correspondence, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - New York City Partnership Information, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Research on Employment and Developments for NYC Communities, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Research on Funding Models for Arts Organizations, 2000-2001 (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Various Program Directories, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Drafts and Releases and Directories of Arts Organizations, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Hotel Ballrooms, Correspondence, Costs for Events, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Correspondence, Press Releases, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Symposia and Panels, Various Correspondence, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Correspondence and Press Releases, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Contact Lists from NYFA and Other Organizations, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Supply Requisitions, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Downtown NYC Restaurant Menus, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Web Domain Registration Forms, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Library of Congress Publishers Information and Correspondence, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Expenses Lists, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Photographs, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Photographs, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Printed Materials, 2001-2005 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - MetaForms (Computer Arts Fellowship Brochures), 2002 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - Posters and Printed and Promotional Material, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Cultural Blueprint for NYC - "The HandPrint Project" Printouts and Brochures, 2005 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Subseries H. Felissimo, 1993-2001; 2 linear feet
    These boxes contain applications to Felissimo, which were handled through NYFA. The applications also contain artist/designer information, press releases, promotional material and some financial material.
    This program was arranged alphabetically by last name of the applicants as the program went on from 1993 to 1998. General files were put at the end of the series and were arranged chronologically.
    This program was funded by the Japanese mail order company Felissimo to award designers who had novel ideas for products that could be sold through Felissimo's mail order catalog.
    - Felissimo - Brief history of Felissimo, The Design Aeard and Fellismo's Involvement with NYFA, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Felissimo - Application folder of Max Burton to Felissimo, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Felissimo - Application of Dalya Luttwak to Felissimo, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Felissimo - Application of Cristina Khuly to Felissimo, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Felissimo - Application of Carolanne Patterson and Sarah MacFadden to Felissimo, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Felissimo - Application of Jessica Griffin and Jim TerMeer (collaboration) to Felissimo, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Felissimo - Application of Aki Hirota to Felissimo, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Felissimo - NYFA Error Letter to R. Haner and D. Hafner (Rejections), 1997 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Felissimo - Information about the Felissimo/NYFA Design Award, 1993-1995 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Felissimo - Panelist information including promotional materials, resumés and some slides and printed booklets, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Felissimo - Panel Research Materials, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Seminar Information/Schedules, Award timelines, 1996-1997 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Felissimo - Postage Service Costs, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Felissimo - Advertising Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Winners with some promotional materials, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Printer Film for Metropolis Magazine, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Felissimo - Printed Promotional Booklets, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Felissimo - Panel Research Materials, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Felissimo - Materials about Felissimo, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Felissimo - Budget and Financial Materials, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Felissimo - Lists of Panels, 1993-1998 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Felissimo - Grant Recipients, 1993-1997 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Felissimo - Printed Promotional Materials, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Felissimo - Printed Promotional Materials, 1995-1997 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Felissimo - Printed Promotional Materials, 1993-1995 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Felissimo - Press Releases, 1993-1998 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Felissimo - Seminars, 1996-1998 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Felissimo - Travel Records, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Winners Lists, Biographies, Letters, Slides, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 47)
    - Felissimo - Applications and Printed Materials, 1995-1998 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Felissimo - Artist Biographies and Press Releases, 1993-1996 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Guidelines, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Felissimo - Agreement for Awards, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Felissimo - Meeting Notes with NYFA, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - Felissimo - "Artists Communities and Residency Programs In the United States," A Study by NYFA, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - Felissimo - Correspondence betweeb Felissimo and Ted Berger, proposals, timelines, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - Felissimo - Panelists lists and charges, 1993-1996 (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - Felissimo - Press releseases and other printed materials, lists of Design Award recipients, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 56)
    - Felissimo - Codes of Ethics for Panelists, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 57)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Recipients incl. Tim Watkins, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 58)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Agreements and timelines, 1996-1998 (Box 30, Folder 59)
    - Felissimo - Award Winners with Artist Information and slides, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 60)
    - Felissimo - Cash Flow, Budgets, 1995-1998 (Box 30, Folder 61)
    - Felissimo - Award Winners, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 62)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Winner Slides, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 63)
    - Felissimo - Edward L. Guttman Application and Design Award Letter, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 64)
    - Felissimo - Michelle Badalich Design Award and Description of Work, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 65)
    - Felissimo - Winners Agreement Forms an Descriptions of Work, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 66)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Winner, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 67)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Winners, Rachel Deitsch, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 68)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Winners, Dorothy Hafner, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 69)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Winners, Richard Currie, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 70)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Winners, Michelle Badalich, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 71)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Winners, Ann Agee, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 72)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Winners, Linnea Gits, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 73)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Winners, Russell Krysiak, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 74)
    - Felissimo - Organization Information, Nomination Committee Information, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Felissimo - Printed Promotional Materials, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Felissimo - Printed Promotional Materials, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Felissimo - Metropolis Magazine Advertisement, Printing Plate, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Felissimo - Notes, Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Felissimo - Prospective Panelist Resumés, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Felissimo - Panel Hotel Information, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Felissimo - Panelist Recommdations, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Felissimo - Acceptance Agreement Forms, Recipients, Tax/Financial Information, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Felissimo - Award Letters, Rejection Letters, Panelist Letters, Correspondence, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Felissimo - Panelist List, Voting Sheets, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Felissimo - Felissimo Design Awards, Press, Panelist Information and Correspondence, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Felissimo - Invoices, Meeting Agendas, Meeting Minutes, Travel Informatio Budget, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Felissimo - Panelist Information, Voting Sheets, Financial Information, Blank Applications, Promotional Materials, 1996-1998 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Felissimo - Francine Gemperle/DigitalInk, Project Information, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Felissimo - Meeting with NYFA, Advertising Contacts, Job Description, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Felissimo - Technology Workshop Information, Sign-Up Sheet, Advertising Contacts, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Felissimo - American Craft Council Library, 1996-1998 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Felissimo - Award Letters, Felissimo Logo Designs, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Felissimo - Design Award Panel, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Subseries I. New York-Israel Cultural Cooperation Commission, 1998-2004; 7 linear feet
    These boxes contain meeting minutes and notes, memorandum, and correspondence created by the commission. A bulk of the subseries consists of applications for the NYICCC grant for fiscal sponsorship of individual artists and organizations. There are also applications for cultural missions to Israel.
    Meeting notes, application materials, and research, notes, memorandum, and correspondence are at the beginning of the subseries, arranged chronologically. Applications for grants and cultural missions are arranged alphabetically and chronologically.
    The New York-Israel Cultural Cooperation Commission was a series of grant programs for fiscal sponsorship of projects and cultural missions to Israel with funds being dispersed by NYFA. The program was meant to foster cooperation between Israel and the people of NYC.
    - New York-Israel Cultural Cooperation Commision (NYICCC) Board Members, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - NYICCC - Memorandum of Intent, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - NYICCC Meeting Notes, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - NYICCC - Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - NYICCC - Board Members Photographs, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - NYICCC - NYICCC Nonprofit Grant Application Form (Blank), 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - NYICCC Issues in Project, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - NYICCC - Empire State Development Corporation (ESDC) Guidelines and Information, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - NYICCC - Letterhead, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - NYICCC - Telephone Log, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - NYICCC - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - NYICCC - Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - NYICCC Funding and Allocations, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - NYICCC Project Calendar, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - NYICCC - Mailing List - Applications, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - NYICCC - Items of Business, Miscellaneous, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - NYICCC - Documents, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - NYICCC - Fiscal Sponsorship, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - NYICCC - Chairman's Report, September, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - NYICCC Meeting Agenda, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - NYICCC Meeting, April 23, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - NYICCC Meeting, June 25, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - NYICCC - Syvia de Swaan Correspondence, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - NYICCC - Press and PR Materials, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - NYICCC - July 1st Meeting, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - NYICCC - August 1st Meeting, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - NYICCC - August 20th Meeting, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - NYICCC - September 23rd Meeting, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - NYICCC - October 20th Meeting, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - NYICCC - November 19th Meeting, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - NYICCC - December 17th Meeting, 2002 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - NYICCC - January 16th Meeting, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - NYICCC - February 25th Meeting, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - NYICCC - April 9th Meeting, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - NYICCC - May 8th Meeting, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - NYICCC - Curators Meeting, June 23rd, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - NYICCC - August 6th Meeting, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - NYICCC - September 16th Meeting, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - NYICCC - G.W. Foundation Meeting, June 12th, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - NYICCC - Program Information and Correspondence, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - NYICCC - 1999 Annual Report (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - The Feminist Press, Inc., 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Yeshiva University Museum of Yeshiva University, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - 92nd Street Y, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - 92nd Street YM-YWHA, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - America Israel Cultural Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - ArtsSweats, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Artists Space, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - The Boys Choir Harlem, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM), 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - CityArts, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - CityParks Foundation - SummerStage, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - CityParks Foundation - SummerStage, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Creative Time, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - The Eli Lemberger Museum of Photography at the Tel Hai Industrial Park, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Garden of Peace International, Corp., 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Herzliya Museum of Art, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - House of Dance Inc. (The Neta Dance Company), 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Infinity Dance Theater, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - International Committee for the Dance Library of Israel, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - The Jerusalem Syphony Orchestra, IBA, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - The Jewish Museum, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - The Jewish Museum, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - The Partnership for Jewish Life, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Peridance Ensemble, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Reshet Eilon International Violin Mastercourse, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Suzanne Dellal Centre for Dance and Theatre, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Temple Beth Israel of Port Washington, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Thread Waxing Space, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - ZGD, Inc., 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - America-Israel Cultural Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - The American Tap Dance Orchestra, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Art in General, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Bat-Dor Studios of Dance, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Bat-Dor Studios of Dance, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn Academy of Music (BAM), 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - CITYarts, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - City Parks Foundation - SummerStage, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - The Drawing Center, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - The Elizabeth Foundation for the Arts, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - The Elizabeth Foundation for the Arts, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - House of Dance, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - The Institute for Contemporary Art/PS 1 Museum nad the Clocktower Gallery, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Interaction Dance Foundation (Interaction Arts, Inc.), 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - International Studio and Curatorial Program/Elizabeth Foundation for the Arts, 2000-2001 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Israel Colloquium, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Israeli Dance Institute, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - IsraRest Foundation, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - IsraRest Foundation, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - The Jerusalem Foundation, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - The Jerusalem Foundation, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Community Center on the Upper West Side, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Community Center on the Upper West Side, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - José Limon Dance Foundation, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - La MaMa Experimental Theatre Club, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Max Waldman Archives dba Carol Greunke, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - The Partnership for Jewish Life, Inc., aka, MAKOR, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - The Perlman Music Program, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Pro Arte Chamber Orchestra of New York, Inc., 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - The Richard G. Rosenthal YM-YWHA of Northern Westchester, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - The Tel Aviv Museum of Art, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Temple Israel of Albany, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Westchester Symphony Orchestra, 2000-2001 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Yeshiva University Museum of Yeshiva University, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - 92nd Street YM-YWHA, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - American Sephardi Federation, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - American Society of the University of Haifa, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - ArtResources Transfer, Inc., 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Bat-Dor Studios of Dance, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Brooklyn Information and Culture, Inc., 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Cunningham Dance Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Cunningham Dance Foundation, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - International Studios and Curatorial Program (ISCP), Elizabeth Foundation for Arts (ETA), 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Jewish Education Services of North America, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - The Jerusalem Foundation, Inc., 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - The Jewish Theological Seminary of America, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - La MaMa Experimental Theatre Club, Inc., 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - La MaMa Experimental Theatre Club, Inc., 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc., 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - National Foundation for Jewish Culture, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - North American Jewish Choral Festival, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Sephardic House, Inc., 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - The SymphonySpace, Inc., 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Tel Aviv, Working Together, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Zamir Choral Foundation, Inc., 2001-2002 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Brooklyn Information and Culture, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Brooklyn Information and Culture, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - The Carnegie Hall Corporation, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Compagnie Faim de Siecle, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Dance Theatre of Harlem, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Haleakala, Inc. dba The Kitchen, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Hebrew Union College - Jewish Institute of Religion, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Hebrew Union College - Jewish Institute of Religion, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Hebrew Union College - Jewish Institute of Religion, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - International Center of Photograph, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - The Jewish Community Center in Manhattan, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - The Joyce Theater Foundation, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - The Joyce Theater Foundation, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc., 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - The Suzanne Dellal Centre for Dance and Theatre, Neve Tzedek, Tel Aviv, 2002-2003 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Apex Art Curatorial Program, 2003-2004 (Box 36, Folder 17)